(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Are you ready?
教えてよ 教えてよ その仕組みを
Tell me, oh tell me, the way it works
僕の中に誰かいるの？
Is there someone else inside of me?
壊れた壊れたよ この世界で
In this world, everything's broken, so broken
君が笑う 何も見えずに
You're laughing, seeing nothing at all
unravel / Lyrics・Composition: TK
壊れた僕なんてさ 息を止めて
Someone as broken as me, holding my breath
ほどけない もうほどけないよ 真実さえ freeze
It won't unravel, it won't unravel anymore, even the truth, freeze
壊せる 壊せない 狂える 狂えない あなたを見つけた
Breakable, unbreakable, going mad, not going mad, I found you
揺れて歪んだ世界にだんだん僕は 透き通って見えなくなって
In a swaying, distorted world, I'm gradually becoming transparent and invisible
見つけないで 僕のことを
Don't find me
見つめないで
Don't look at me
誰かが描いた世界で あなたを傷つけたくはないよ
In the world that someone else imagined, I don't want to hurt you
unravel
#NODOWNTIME2024
揺れた歪んだ世界にだんだん僕は
In a distorted world that's swaying, I gradually...
透き通って見えなくなって
...become transparent and invisible.
見つけないで僕のことを
Please don't find me.
見つめないで
Don't look at me.
誰かが仕組んだ孤独な罠に
In a lonely trap that someone set up...
無限に広がる孤独が絡まる
Infinitely spreading loneliness gets entangled.
無邪気に笑った記憶が刺さって
Memories of innocently laughing stab through me.
動けない、動けない、動けない、動けない、動けない、動けないよ
I can't move, can't move, can't move, can't move, can't move, I can't move!
UNRAVEL GHOUL!
変わってしまった 変えられなかった
I've changed, I couldn't change it.
二つが絡まる 二人が滅びる
The two are entangled, the two of us perish.
壊せる 壊せない 狂える 狂えない
Can be broken, can't be broken; can go mad, can't go mad.
あなたを汚せないよ
I can't defile you.
揺れた歪んだ世界にだんだん僕は
In a distorted world that's swaying, I gradually...
透き通って見えなくなって
...become transparent and invisible.
見つけないで僕のことを
Please don't find me.
見つめないで
Don't look at me.
誰かが仕組んだ孤独な罠に
In a lonely trap that someone set up...
未来が解けてしまう前に
...before the future unravels.
思い出して僕のことを
Remember me...
鮮やかなまま
...while I'm still vivid.
忘れないで 忘れないで
Don't forget me, don't forget me.
変わってしまったことにパラライズ
Paralyzed by the fact that I've changed.
変えられないことだらけのパラダイス
A paradise full of things that can't be changed.
覚えていて僕のことを
Remember me.
教えて 教えて
Tell me, tell me.
僕の中に誰かいるの？
Is there someone inside of me?
皆さーん！ Hey everybody!
Everyone! Hey everybody!
It's me, Mori Calliope from Hololive English -Myth-,
everybody's favorite hardworking Shinigami,
back in action today with a brand new show for all of you guys
that I've been working super, super hard for.
I hope you guys are as excited as I am.
This is my official-official, officially official,
my second birthday live, official 3D live show.
I hope you guys are super, super hyped for it because,
oh man, there's so much good stuff I can't wait to show you.
But there's a special rule for today's live.
And that rule is 'NO DOWN TIME', which means,
which means, I mean, there's no down time.
There's no slow anything, no slow songs,
no slow MCs, no slow Mori.
100% 派手にぶちかまそうぜ！みたいな感じ。
100% like "Let's kick things off flashy!"
Going real crazy. That's why you gotta use the hashtag,
#NODOWNTIME2024 and post a bunch of screenshots.
Can you do that? A bunch of screenshots and your thoughts,
screenshots and your thoughts about this show.
And I'd be really, really happy if you did that,
because we gotta lot of great guests,
we gotta lot of great performances, and not to mention,
we have a great stage.
Would you like to take a look at the stage with me?
Take a look at the Underdome... Underworld Dome...
I haven't come up with a name for it yet, but isn't it great?
It's a special secret place that I found in the Underworld,
where the moon sometimes comes down on the 4th of April,
which happens to be my birthday.
So I figured it would be the perfect setting
for all of us to have a great show together.
I invited a bunch of my friends, and it's gonna be amazing.
There's a lot of great surprises ahead.
Additionally, um...
I can see a bunch of you in the crowd,
I know you're cheering for me. Hey, what's up, skeletons?
Except you look a little more human-shaped. Congratulations on that.
But I'm looking forward to doing my best for you guys.
And as a matter of fact, the next song...
the next song is one that I know you guys have really wanted me
to perform for a long time. And I did perform it before at Fes,
but this time, I want to try and perform it in a way
that is even more explosive and Mori-like in my own home.
I hope that you will enjoy it.
So everybody, please listen to the next song
which is my brand new song that you guys
should definitely stream and listen to a lot
if you haven't had time and check out the MV
for because the art is amazing.
That song is called Overkill.
Check it out.
テメェの所為です
It's your fault
Overkill
Lyrics: Mori Calliope / Yuki Tsujimura
Composition-Arrangement: Yuki Tsujimura / NEG (MEGMETAL)
どの子が 好き？ 小ボコに決めた
Which girl do you like? I've decided to wreck her
角度を調節 覚悟微調節
Adjusting the angle, fine-tuning my resolve
飽きたらポイから Place any bets
Once I'm bored, I toss it, so place any bets
Decide who is special and discard the rest
Gambler by nature Chips start to stack
Racing lovely animals until they crack
やいのやいの貼り付け Parasite
Hanging on with all that noise, Parasite
ヤンデレッテル テメェの所為です
Yandere label, it's all your fault
Blackout breakdown Toss it when you’re out of love
やっちゃえ いっちゃえ I can tell you’re not impressed
Do it, go for it, I can tell you’re not impressed
右向け右 左向け左
Turn right to the right, turn left to the left
Liver etc but why the abyss?
飽きたらポイから Harness worthless dolls
Once I'm bored, I toss it, harness worthless dolls
よってたかっていらっしゃい
Come one, come all, gather 'round
Gambler by nature Chips start to stack
Racing lovely animals until they crack
Beautiful dreams await modest hearts
Close your eyes and all you'll see is black
才能 サイコパスを気味たい
Talent, I want to taste the psychopath
あっちまったの 後悔の Fever
It's happened, the fever of regret
Always starving 時間の無駄無駄
Always starving, a waste of time
やっちゃえ いっちゃえ I can tell you’re not impressed
Do it, go for it, I can tell you’re not impressed
宣戦布告 こちとら最下層
Declaration of war, we're at the very bottom
どうにかなりそう どうにでもなりそう
I'm about to lose it, anything could happen
太っ腹な Lonely lonely trouble in paradise
Generous, lonely lonely trouble in paradise
偽り 覆う 殻 もぎ取って
Tear off the shell that covers the lies
見下してやるわ
I'll look down on you
やいのやいの貼り付け Parasite
Hanging on with all that noise, Parasite
ヤンデレッテル テメェの所為です
Yandere label, it's all your fault
Blackout breakdown Toss it when you’re out of love
やっちゃえ いっちゃえ I'm the one that's not impressed
Do it, go for it, I'm the one that's not impressed
テメェの所為です 死ぬまで離れないわ
It's all your fault, I'll never leave you until I die
パーっと光って ぱらり開くわ
A flash of light, and it'll open up
Let's go!
HEAVY DAY
Lyrics/Composition: Daisuke Ishiwatari
Detonator
will come out of nowhere yeah
Trick. Cheat. Fraud. Lie. Sulfur in the air
So let it be, oh let it be says all debaters
Six times knocking on the door
No response, but hey you're already Back to Back!
Death comes riding on a midnight train
Back to Back! Conscience is screaming to the end
Back to Back! Can no longer pretend
Back to Back! I can no longer pretend
Give me a break, you damned
Just wanna get my dice again
Blazing down, what a heavy day
Now, you hear the rumble from the ground
Now, you hear the rumble from the ground yeah
Trick, Cheat, Fraud, Lie
Clown is dancing around yeah
So let it be, oh let it be, seems I'm the traitor
Six times knocking on the door
One last chance you've got to stand
Back to Back!
Death comes riding on a midnight train
Conscience is screaming to the end
Back to Back!
Can not let anyone do it again
I can no longer pretend
Give me a break, you damned
Just wanna get back my dice again
Blazing down.
What a heavy day
We made a contract with a clown and had a high old time
No body doubted his true purpose, oh yeah
Not knowing we had given up everything we had left
All odds and options denied trapped here in this dead end
Back to Back!
Death comes riding on a midnight train
Conscience is screaming to the end
Back to Back!
Blade is already on your jugular vein
It's now or never, last chance...
...to stand
Give me a break you damned
Just wanna get back my dice again
Blazing down.
What a heavy day
Ina, Ina, Ina, Ina!
Ina-ninas, my Inanis.
Thank you so much for coming and singing Heavy Day together with me! It was so fun!
Calli, happy birthday!
Thank you for inviting me today.
The stage looks great!
Those pillars of fire were hot, though.
Yeah, that's right. You know they're hot, just like our intense GG vibes and our synergy.
This is, this is maybe... I don't know, I think that we've...
...you've been at almost every single one of my birthday lives...
...so I just want to say sincerely, thank you from the bottom of my heart, Ina-ninas.
Keep it up, and good luck with the rest of the show.
Bye-bye! Wishing you all the best!
Bye-bye Ina! Thank you so much for coming!
Well, we have a bunch more guests that are coming...
...but I can't allow myself to rest for even a moment because you guys, the theme is hashtag no downtime.
So I'm just gonna be here, jogging in place, jogging in place.
If I allow myself to rest, then it's false advertising, right Dead Beats? That's what it is, false advertising.
So let's go! Keep it moving, keep it moving!
No breaks, no breaks, no breaks, no breaks on the Mori train!
On to the next! What could it be? What could it be?
爆笑
Bakushou (Laughter)
Lyrics・Composition:syudou
圧倒的に足す人のとか 有耶無耶ったって囃してやってよ
Those who overwhelmingly add things, cheer them on even if it's vague.
結局誰が悪いかなんて 知らず存ぜぬの味方のし合い
In the end, who's to blame? A game of playing favorites by feigning ignorance.
人の背に立つ 瀬に立つ貴方の目 その目、その目が嫌い
Standing on others' backs, your eyes standing on the edge. Those eyes, I hate those eyes.
またアンチで呟け僻み達 そりゃ勝っても負けても痛みなし
Anti-fans tweeting their prejudices again. Well, there's no pain whether you win or lose.
あんなにも作れないまま あんなにも得られないままで
Remaining unable to create that much, remaining unable to obtain that much.
その顔じゃない...
Not that face...
I miss you.
ウハハハ　仰せのまま
Uhahaha, as you wish
惨めな奴らに唾吐いた
Spitting on those miserable wretches
ガハハハ　彼と一緒に
Gahahaha, together with him
哀れみ込めた愛の賛歌
A hymn of love filled with pity
気にならない　気づきもしない
I don't care, I don't even notice
笑ってしまうぜ不完全体
I can't help but laugh, you incomplete thing
この意味が分かるまではただ
Until you understand the meaning of this, just...
静かに笑ってんだ
...keep laughing quietly.
これを止めろだ　そこ代わって死ねだ
Stop this, or swap places and die
いつのお野菜も残しちゃって
Always leaving your vegetables behind
俺の全部を喰らいな　心して
Eat everything of mine, prepare yourself
けど一番右のさ、お前が同じ
But the one on the far right... you're the same
Oh baby ただ笑って
Oh baby, just laugh
独り震えて歌歌って
Singing while trembling alone
俺をそいつが飼い慣らす
That thing will tame me
お前も、アンデッドも
You, and the undead too
ウハハハ　晴れ行く情緒
Uhahaha, emotions clearing up
西の魔女くるリスペクト
Respecting the witch of the west
ガハハハ　ガチで自称
Gahahaha, seriously self-proclaimed
最下位果ての心酔者
An adorer at the bottom of the pile
空文じゃない　話したくない
It's not empty words, I don't want to talk
狂っても大概に三年後
Even if I go crazy, keep it within reason, three years later
邪論などかき消すほどほら
Look, enough to drown out all those wrong views
誰もが笑ってんだ
Everyone is laughing.
あなたが見てきた光たちは
The lights you have seen
今もまだここを強く握って
Are still gripping this place tightly
苦しませる
Causing pain
「笑われる」「笑わせる」の溝
The gap between being laughed at and making others laugh
ほとばしって聞かせてやるから
It overflows, so I'll let you hear it
この名前くらいは覚えて帰れ
At least remember this name before you go home!
ウハハハ　仰せのまま
Uhahaha, as you wish
惨めな奴らに唾吐いた
Spitting on those miserable wretches
ガハハハ　彼と一緒に
Gahahaha, together with him
哀れみ込めた愛の賛歌
A hymn of love filled with pity
ウハハハ　辞めて頂戴
Uhahaha, please stop
極一丁はまだつまらんさ
One song is still boring
ガハハハ　芸で上等
Gahahaha, superior with my craft
これが答えだ文句あるか
This is the answer, any complaints?
成果試験　乗るか剃るか
Achievement test, win or lose
出世人生商売繁盛
Successful life, business prosperity
振り向けず登り続けただ
Just keep climbing without looking back
天上天下独りだって出囃子は鳴ってんだ
Even if I'm all alone in this world, my theme song is playing!
答えはどこへ
Where is the answer?
探して
Looking for it
Where's my soul?
It's like a fear　悪い夢の様で
It's like a fear, just like a bad dream
目覚めても all I've got is bones
Even when I wake, all I've got is bones
I'm in a panic? Get out, hurry
Oh, there are mysteries and miseries
Dead or alive　狭間に揺られて
Dead or alive, swayed in the gap
彷徨えば right to the hell
If I wander, it's right to the hell
孤独の招待　獲物の正体
Invitation to solitude, the identity of the prey
踊る 1, 2, 3 steps on this dark stage
Dancing 1, 2, 3 steps on this dark stage
Raise your flag, march on, fight　仮面の淵へ
Raise your flag, march on, fight, to the edge of the mask
手を掛けたなら骨が鳴るのみ
If you reach out, only the bones will rattle
Wars and swords, tears and blood　溢る力が
Wars and swords, tears and blood, the overflowing power...
不意に笑い出した
...suddenly started laughing.
答えはどこへ
Where is the answer?
探して
Looking for it
Where's my soul? Where's my heart?
現実（いま）に呑まれてく
Being swallowed by reality
Don't hesitate, go this way
Don't stay
理解らない　構わない
I don't understand, I don't care
紛い物振るっても
Even if I brandish a fake
ただこの世界を生き抜けよ
Just survive in this world
無くした哀しみがまた疼いて
The lost sadness aches again
Misery-World
漆黒の空　冷たく midnight / 夜の闇は always drives me mad
Pitch black sky, cold midnight / The darkness of night always drives me mad
Where is the star now? I found the star now / But it's so beautiful, I'm so doubtful
戸惑いの中宿る desire
Desire dwelling amidst confusion
見渡せば sky, and land and sea
Looking around, sky and land and sea
ハイエの嗤い　他愛ない支配
The hyena's sneer, a trivial dominion
登る 1, 2, 3 steps to the royal throne
Climbing 1, 2, 3 steps to the royal throne
Cast a spell, call them up　絶望を呼べ
Cast a spell, call them up, summon the despair
虚しさに酔い　兵たちが舞う
Intoxicated by emptiness, the soldiers dance
Shouts and barks, grief and death　戦慄く者に
Shouts and barks, grief and death, to those who tremble...
無慈悲を振り下ろせ
...bring down your ruthlessness!
無情を行け
Go through the heartlessness
暴いて
Uncover it
Break it all!
Break it all, take it all.
手に入れろすべてを
Obtain it all
I just pray, or just play?
そうじゃない 止まらない
That's not it, I won't stop
消えない疑念抱いて
Embracing doubts that won't fade
失くした物を取り戻せよ
Recover what you've lost
嗚呼 それさえ覆う狂気にまみれても
Ah, even if you're covered in the madness that shrouds it
Crazy World
見えない心と確かに在る体
An invisible heart and a body that certainly exists
信じたいものを己に誓え
Vow to yourself the things you want to believe in
真実を捨てて走れ
Discard the truth and run
Where's my soul? Where's my heart?
その意志を信じて
Believe in that will
Don't hesitate, go this way
理解らない 構わない
I don't understand, I don't care
夢でも現実でも
Whether it's a dream or reality
ただこの世界を生き抜こう
Let's just survive this world
さあ何処まででもこの足が行く限り
Come, as far as these legs will take us
Misery World
BLACK MEMORY
Lyrics・Composition: 山中拓也
Lyrics・Composition: Takuya Yamanaka
Get get it up, get get it up
本当はもう聞き飽きた 現実からの逃避
Truthfully, I'm tired of hearing it, escaping from reality
大体はエゴロジスト 悦に浸っていたいさ
Mostly ecologists, just wanting to indulge in self-satisfaction
迷宮なんてさ 願ってもない 叶やしないさ
A labyrinth, it's not even a wish, it won't come true
葬り去りゆく夜の心地は 非常に残酷な自問自答
The feeling of a night being buried is a very cruel self-questioning
幸か不幸かは 自分の眼にしか見えないさ
Happiness or misfortune, can only be seen through one's own eyes
No one gets close to me
BLACK MEMORY
どうなったっていい まだわからない世界で
It doesn't matter what happens, in a world I still don't understand
滲む Ah oh, Ah oh 叫ぶ
Blurred Ah oh, Ah oh I scream
どうなったっていいから 僕を壊さないで
I don't care what happens, so don't break me
醒ませ Ah oh, Ah oh 限界突破見せてやるさ
Awaken Ah oh, Ah oh, I'll show you how I break the limits
Get get it up, get get it up
Like a loser, いつだって満たされないよ
Like a loser, I'm never satisfied
きっとその方が強いからさ
Surely that's why I'm stronger
迷宮なんてさ 出口も無いし 終わりのないさ
A labyrinth, there's no exit and no end
Oh Shit!!
此の中に溢れ出す 異常に価値のない有象無象
Overflowing inside here, extraordinarily worthless commoners
関係ない絆 あなたの心で
Irrelevant bonds, in your heart
BLACK MEMORY
どうなったっていい まだわからない世界で
It doesn't matter what happens, in a world I still don't understand
滲む Ah oh, Ah oh 叫ぶ
Blurred Ah oh, Ah oh I scream
どうなったっていいから 僕を壊さないで
I don't care what happens, so don't break me
醒ませ Ah oh, Ah oh 限界突破見せてやるさ
Awaken Ah oh, Ah oh, I'll show you how I break the limits
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Everybody get it up! Come on!
Get get it up, get get it up
一瞬の迷いも見せない 僕の独り舞台に落とすのは
Not showing a moment's hesitation, what I drop onto my solo stage is...
僕の喉が派手に渇くとするのは
If my throat were to become intensely parched,
渇望と希望の二層を既に離した
I've already let go of the two layers of craving and hope.
記憶だけ
Only memories.
BLACK MEMORY
人生は守るべきもの求めてきていて
Life has been seeking things worth protecting,
いつか Oh Oh Oh Oh 越える
And one day, it will surpass them.
どなただっていいとかもう言わせないよ
I won't let anyone say "it can be just anyone" anymore.
Oh 響け Oh Oh Oh Oh
Oh, resound!
全身全霊かけてやるさ
I'll give it my heart and soul.
Get get it up! Get get it up!
HAPPY BIRTHDAY MORI-SENPAI!
Ah... tchk-tchk-tchk-ka
Yeah, rrr-rrr-rrr-ah!
Silly bakka silly b- Serious na shit, lemme shake it up.
Do what I want shit gotta reckon ya. Got a thirst for the worst lookin' back on a cheap-a.
Silly bakka silly bakka, silly ass lookin' shit, gotta shake it up!
Wanna be lookin' freaks all they do is talk, getcha head out ya ass like what you gotta hot, huh?
毎度毎度神頼み
Praying to God every single time,
冤罪せんわそんな奴
I won't pardon a guy like that.
あーもう情状酌量の余地なし即死刑ハイ
Ah, there's no room for leniency, death penalty right now, go!
地獄まで行きなさい
Go to hell!
今すぐにお逝きなさい
Die right now!
メラメラ Burning all day 真夏の楽園
Flaming hot, burning all day, a midsummer paradise.
メラメラ 焼かれて 灰になるまで
Flaming hot, scorched until you turn to ash.
メラメラ 虜にさせて さあ踊り狂っちゃって
Flaming hot, I'll captivate you, now dance like crazy!
火炙りパラダイス Go up and down
Burning at the stake paradise, go up and down.
Silly bakka silly b- Serious na shit, lemme shake it up.
Do what I want shit you know what I got. Might be the pinnacle of cynical but first keep the mic high.
And may I just remind you act a fool this god'll find you.
Da-du-da-du-du-da-du-du-da-da-du-da-du-da
C-A-double-L-O-U You already know Scythe at the ready slow and steady give em a show.
They wanna get real close, can't learn to let go.
Flame and dance with the R.I.P. set a look up below.
Slay to the beat in the street rather than roast and slam 'em back 'til the sunrise and have a low slow.
Sleepin' to the next night you know where we go. Only fast folks keep the pace- Shinigami flow alright?
Shinigami flow alright?
Ah, maitanomi again, gimme mo' that's all about,
ほらまだまだ足りない
See, it's still not enough.
Spent all day beneath the sun sun sun sun sun
Sub is blastin' out da-dan-dan-dan-dan
I don't care sing a la la la la la
Will not lose time, you don't gotta run
愛は痛い苦しい苦しい
Love is painful, it hurts, it hurts.
灼熱に飛び込んで Give it to ya, give it to ya
Dive into the scorching heat, give it to ya, give it to ya.
みなさん！ You got the rest!
Everyone! You got the rest!
Mori and Kobo's in the building, so you know you're already dead.
You're dead!
Tchk-tchk-ka, tchk-tchk-ka
地獄まで行きなさい
Go to hell!
火炙りパラダイス Go up and down
Burning at the stake paradise, go up and down.
Boko-boko-boko-boko-boko-boko Kobo!
Woohoo!
Kobo, thank you so much for singing with me!
Yo! Whoa! Ah!
Thank you as well!
Kobo wish you a happy birthday, best birthday!
Yeah, you know, you spit some flames.
You're a great rapper actually, Kobo, you should do more rap I think!
Hey! It was so difficult, but...
Kobo is a pro rapper and, yeah, you know...
We are a one blood right? Yeah, daddy?
Yeah! Singing together with you was awesome!
High five!
Kana, you nailed it! That was great, wow.
わあ、すごい、素敵な後輩。
Wow, incredible, what a wonderful junior.
You're amazing, wow.
Maybe following in Mori's footsteps a little bit? I don't know.
Release the Kobo Mixtape!
Start the Kobo SoundCloud!
Yeah! And Daddy, since I'm here, let's take a picture! Okay?
Please, please! Okay, let's...
Okay, let's make a Kobo pose first, okay?
Okay, picture time! Let's go, yeah!
Right in front of you, okay?
You kids these days with your... your always taking photos...
...and your hashtags...
Speaking of hashtags, take a screenshot of us...
...and then make sure that you use the hashtag...
...it's the one time where I won't feel embarrassed...
...if you spam my hashtag on Twitter/X, so please do it!
Strike a pose! Cheese!
Yeah! Get fancy with it!
Blue and pink is the best combination!
What do you think? I think we look pretty good together.
Okay, looks good, right? Uh...
One more, Daddy, cute pose, okay? Say...
Say "UwU", okay, Daddy? Yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah...
UwU, UwU, like that, okay?
Okay, let's go! Cute pose!
UwU!
Okay, looks good, right?
Thanks again, Daddy, for inviting me!
Kobo wants to go to the mall with Mommy, okay? Bye-bye!
やった! See you later, Kobo! Bye-bye! Thanks again!
Score! See you later, Kobo! Bye-bye! Thanks again!
Wait, no down... no downtime, no downtime, no downtime! Hold on...
Okay, no downtime!
We keep it moving! We keep it moving onto the next!
I'm gonna die...
努力 未来 A BEAUTIFUL STAR
Effort, future, A BEAUTIFUL STAR
ランドリー 今日はガラ空きでラッキーデイ
The laundry is empty today, a lucky day
かったりぃ 油汚れもこれでバイバイ
So boring, say bye-bye to oil stains with this
誰だ 誰だ 頭の中 呼びかける声は
Who is it? Who is it? The voice calling in my head
あれが欲しい これが欲しい と歌っている
Singing, "I want that, I want this"
幸せになりたい 楽して生きていたい
I want to be happy, I want to live an easy life
この手に掴みたい あなたのその胸の中
I want to grab hold of it inside your chest
胸の中
Inside your chest
ハッピーで埋め尽くして
Fill it all up with happy
レスト・イン・ピースまで行こうぜ
Let's go until Rest In Peace
いつか見た地獄もいいところ
The hell I saw once wasn't so bad either
愛をばら撒いて
Scattering love all around
アイラブユー貶してくれ
I love you, disparage me
全部奪って笑ってくれマイハニー
Take it all and laugh for me, my honey
努力 未来 A BEAUTIFUL STAR
Effort, future, A BEAUTIFUL STAR
なんか忘れちゃってんだ
I've forgotten something
努力 未来 A BEAUTIFUL STAR
Effort, future, A BEAUTIFUL STAR
4443で外れる炭酸水
Carbonated water that goes flat at 4443
ハングリー 拗らせて吐きそうな人生
Hungry, making life feel like I'm gonna vomit
止まない雨はないより先に その傘をくれよ
Before "there's no rain that won't stop", give me that umbrella
あれが欲しい これが欲しい 全て欲しい ただ虚しい
I want that, I want this, I want it all, it's just empty
幸せになりたい 楽して生きていたい
I want to be happy, I want to live an easy life
全部めちゃくちゃにしたい 何もかも消し去りたい
I want to mess it all up, I want to erase everything
あなたのその胸の中
Inside that chest of yours
胸の中
Inside your chest
ラッキーで埋め尽くして
Fill it all up with lucky
レスト・イン・ピースまで行こうぜ
Let's go until Rest In Peace
良い子だけ迎える天国じゃ
In a heaven that only welcomes good kids
どうも生きらんない
I just can't live
アイラブユー貶して
I love you, disparage me
奪って 笑ってくれマイハニー
Take it, and laugh for me, my honey
努力 未来 A BEAUTIFUL STAR
Effort, future, A BEAUTIFUL STAR
なんか忘れちゃってんだ
I've forgotten something
ハッピー ラッキー こんにちはベイビー
Happy, lucky, hello baby
良い子でいたい そりゃつまらない
I want to be a good kid, but that's boring
ハッピー ラッキー こんにちはベイビー ソースイート
Happy, lucky, hello baby, so sweet
努力 未来 A BEAUTIFUL STAR
Effort, future, A BEAUTIFUL STAR
なんかすごい良い感じ
Somehow it feels really good
努力 未来 A BEAUTIFUL STAR
Effort, future, A BEAUTIFUL STAR
しょっぱいぜ
It's salty
初めて嗅いで舐めた出会い
The encounter I first smelled and tasted
自暴自棄です 平均的な正論がビンボー
I'm desperate; average sound logic is poor
いらっしゃいませ
Welcome
ニンニク増して目指して健康体
Aiming for a healthy body with extra garlic
腹歌満たしてる
Filling up with a belly song
悠長さ 無知なフリして当たっちゃって
Leisureliness, hitting it while pretending to be ignorant
欠点です 現状把握そこから中断中
It's a flaw; understanding the current situation, suspended from there
もう譲渡 見せびらかし合いましょ
Already a transfer; let's show off to each other
劣等感も変えられやしないって
They say inferiority complexes won't change
わかってるからぁ？
Do you understand?
直感で自己中な
Intuitive and selfish
理解不能プレイヤー
Incomprehensible player
求められたなら惨事会
If requested, a disaster meeting
くだらん口喧嘩でマシになった
It got better with a stupid quarrel
もっともっと 意外と辛いのに
More, more, even though it's surprisingly painful
うざいくらい叫んだって喰らったって譲れない日々よ
Days I won't give up, even if I scream or take it until it's annoying
栄養になって また汚しあえ
Become nourishment and soil each other again
わかんなくて 我慢なって脊髄反射の涙腺は
I don't understand, I can't take it, and my tear ducts reflect my spinal cord
濁った声で歌えば感謝です
If I sing with a muddy voice, I'm grateful
試したいわ あたたかくて
I want to try it, it's so warm
絶体絶命な 夜は気持ちいい
The desperate nights feel so good
平凡な生活 夢見たけど
I dreamed of an ordinary life, but...
先手必勝が 気持ちいいな
Winning by taking the initiative feels good
帰ってすぐに水やり 人間の営み
Watering plants right after returning home, human activities
実のところ恵まれても虚無感が友だち
To be honest, even if blessed, a sense of emptiness is my friend
眠気覚まし耳打ち 飲み干すまで合図
Whispering to wake up, a signal until I drink it all
仲良しこよし直感で
Best friends, by intuition
自己中な
Selfish
理解不能プレイヤー
Incomprehensible player
求められたなら惨事会
If requested, a disaster meeting
細かいご指摘も有り難き
I appreciate even the smallest pointers
結局どこ開いてしまうのに
After all, where am I going to open up...
うざいくらい叫んだって喰らったって譲れない日々よ
Days I won't give up, even if I scream or take it until it's annoying
栄養になって また汚しあえ
Become nourishment and soil each other again
わかんなくて 我慢なくて脊髄反射の涙腺は
I don't understand, I can't take it, and my tear ducts reflect my spinal cord
濁った声で歌えば感謝です
If I sing with a muddy voice, I'm grateful
試したいわ あたたかくて
I want to try it, it's so warm
絶体絶命な 夜は気持ちいい
The desperate nights feel so good
平凡な生活 夢見たけど
I dreamed of an ordinary life, but...
先手必勝が 気持ちいいな
Winning by taking the initiative feels good
ただ穏やかでいたい
I just want to be calm
誰にも迷惑かけたくはないと思うが
I don't want to trouble anyone, but...
迷惑をかけたくなければ
If you don't want to cause trouble
死なないとなんて言わせないわ
I won't let you say you have to die
単純明快でした
It was simple and clear
うざいくらい叫んだって喰らったって譲れない日々よ
Days I won't give up, even if I scream or take it until it's annoying
栄養になって また汚しあえ
Become nourishment and soil each other again
わかんなくて 我慢なくて脊髄反射の涙腺は
I don't understand, I can't take it, and my tear ducts reflect my spinal cord
濁った声で歌えば感謝です
If I sing with a muddy voice, I'm grateful
言いたいことジャンケンで負けちゃって
Losing at rock-paper-scissors for what I want to say
まずは実感まで 拵え
First, prepare yourself until you feel it
すぐ吐けなくて 呆気なくて脊髄反射の涙腺は
Can't spit it out right away, empty-headed, and my tear ducts reflect my spinal cord
萎んだ脳で歌えば感謝です
If I sing with a shriveled brain, I'm grateful
だりいし痒いし薄っぺらい下らないことで歌えて勝った
It's dull, itchy, thin, and stupid, but I won by singing
賄えないじゃ満たされない不快感
An unsatisfiable discomfort if I can't cover it
暴れる脳は暴れるでも慣れない
The thrashing brain thrashes, but I don't get used to it
傷にはセッションで絶頂で健康体 気持ちいいな
Sessions for wounds, peaks for a healthy body, it feels good
Yay! Thank you so much everybody! That was Zanki, Time Left.
Speaking of time left, there is none. There's no time left!
But, uh, this has been a really, really amazing "No Down Time" live show with you guys and all of the amazing guests that came here.
So thank you so much for coming to support me and have a great live show. My fourth one. Wow, my fourth...
...my fourth birthday here in Holo, and I'm so, so happy to have gotten this chance to celebrate it with you here in the Underworld.
It was fantastic. But, you know, it is my birthday, and when it comes to birthdays, there's... there's something important to announce.
What does everybody announce during their birthday? Uh... hold on, I'm thinking.
I don't know. I forgot. I forgot.
Wait, it's... I remember, I remember! I remember!
Rebeats, I'm a little scatterbrained, I'm sorry. It's because I'm excited.
Birthday goods! Ta-da!
Birthday Celebration 2024
Hey everybody!
This, this is definitely a set that I'm...
...super excited to introduce to you guys.
By the way, check it out, me playing the bass.
Hey, it's not a lie...
...because for my birthday, I bought myself a bass!
Yay! I'm going to start learning again.
I'm not a fake bass player.
Stop! Don't call me that. I'm not a fake bass player.
ボコボコにするぞ。
I'll beat you up.
...okay?
It's cool. The illustration's cool and...
...and it's on a couple of these goods.
紹介しますね。
I guess I'll introduce them to you.
Next.
So, um, first of all, first and foremost...
Eternal Rest Square Cushion!
Would you like to sleep forever, Dead Beats?
Well, good news for you. I have a cushion that is...
...extremely comfy and super special...
...and has a picture of me playing the bass on it.
You're going to fall asleep immediately...
...but I can't guarantee that because of legal stuff.
Um, check it out. The art is beautiful.
Um, it's high quality and amazing.
Um, I think it's high quality.
I hope that you enjoy it.
Um, and you can take lots of naps with it.
I wish I could take naps. I can't take naps.
Next!
Next slide is... Hey, Dead Beats!
Do you guys like fashion? I like fashion.
There are designer brands I can't name because legal.
However, in the underworld, we have our own brands.
I have collaborated with one of my favorites...
...to create this Underworldian Designer Muffler!
I consider this like the 'Rizz Pack' birthday goods.
Check it out. Calliope Mori symbol.
Um, you can find other Dead Beats out in the wild...
...without just having Mori on your shirt, you know?
It's very convenient. And the tag is also super cute.
So make sure you get snug for fall and winter.
I hope you guys enjoy wearing this...
...and adding it to your wardrobe.
Next slide, please!
Additionally, we have... Dead Beat Honorary Ring!
Do not get it twisted, this is not a marriage ring.
結婚してないよ！
I'm not marrying you!
Dead Beats, I'm not going to marry you.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, too busy. I'm too busy.
But if you'd like, you could go ahead...
...and purchase this Dead Beat Honorary Ring...
...so that you can find other Dead Beats in the wild.
It makes it a little bit easier, right?
And plus, if it doesn't fit on your finger...
...you can go ahead and put it on a necklace.
And it's still very, very fashionable.
I really love the design. It reminds me of you guys.
I hope you'll enjoy wearing this very special ring.
And next!
Last, we have the "Your Last Shot"...
...shot glass set. Go find a Dead Beat and cheers!
Drink some alcohol that reminds you of Mori.
But they're very cute. It's a cute set.
I want to see them at every birthday party.
Every Dead Beat party in general.
Use these a lot to go wild and party. No downtime!
Um, I guess that's about it.
Next slide, please!
Um, we also have a situation voice.
It's called "Backstage with Calliope".
I don't know what this sounds like yet.
But maybe if I see you after the show...
...I might remember it. I don't know.
Maybe because it's yet to happen.
Also, if you get the full set, you get a special...
...secret voice. Please look forward to that.
And next slide!
For the entire full set, if you buy the whole thing...
...you will get a signed card by me!
Mori Calliope. And I'm signing all of them.
I'm signing every single card because you're great.
I want everybody to get a chance to get my signature.
I've been making it really easy for you guys recently.
But this one I definitely will be signing just for you.
You will get a hand-signed postcard from me.
Um, so yeah, please look forward to it.
And next slide, please!
Here's the full set and everything you get with it.
The cart will open as soon as the stream is over.
So make sure that you check it out.
You don't need to be fast because I'm signing all.
But make sure that you grab yours today! Woo!
So that is the... that's the merch situation.
Those are my birthday goods. I'm very happy with them.
I can't wait to receive mine, I hope you're excited.
Now, we have something else I want to show you.
A very special PV some of you may have seen.
It's about something really, really awesome...
...and I'm very excited about it.
So let's watch it!
PV、どうぞ！
Please watch the PV!
Yahoo!
ハーレイ・クインか...
Harley Quinn...
ゴッサム・シティの犯罪王、ジョーカーのパートナー。
Accomplice to The Joker, known as the Gotham City's Clown Prince of Crime
完璧じゃん、プリンちゃん！
Oh that's perfect, Puddin'!
こんなのは長い長いショーの導入だ。
This is just a long introduction to the show.
今の世界は醜く、
The world we know is so hideous and...
何より...不公平だ。
above of all, unfair.
A world connected by the "Gate"
Get down!
あなたたち5人には、ある任務についてもらう。
The five of you will be assigned a mission.
The Super-Villains are sent to ISEKAI
任務？
A mission?
平和のための任務だ。
A peace-keeping mission.
平和？俺たちが？
Us? Peace?
キャスティングを誤ったな。
They've made casting errors for sure.
最恐！
Take that!
イカれてやがる。
She's nuts.
俺、頑張る。
Do my best, me.
我々王国と帝国の戦争は、すでに数十年に及んでいる。
The war between our kingdom and the Empire has been going on for decades.
どうすればこの軍勢を止められる？
How do we defeat their troops?
俺たちが出向き戦えば、瞬く間に平和になる！
If we go out and fight, there will be peace in an instant!
この方たちを信じてみても良いのではないかと。
I think we should trust them.
何？チラチラ見てたよね、アタシのこと。
Hey, you were eyeing me earlier
とにかく今は、この国と有効関係を結ぶことが先決だ。
We need to establish a friendly relationship with them first.
この戦争を終わらせようではないか！
Let us put an end to this war!
ひとまず憂さ晴らしに、帝国の奴らをぶっ潰す。
I will knock 'em out to blow off steam.
じゃ、始めちゃう？
So, shall we kick it off?
Ending Theme "Go-Getters" by Mori Calliope
The Super-Villains'
Pulse-pounding adventure
Begins!!
SUICIDE SQUAD ISEKAI
Streaming 2024.
待ってて、プリンちゃん。
Don't worry, puddin'
アタシ、絶対にプリンちゃんの所に帰るから。
I will come back to you...
Yeah, everybody! Woo!
So, I have been chosen to sing the ending theme
for the TV anime, Suicide Squad Isekai,
to air from July.
I'm so excited about this. I waited so long to tell you guys about it.
And I know I already did tell you about it,
but even saying it now, it feels like a dream.
I mean, even when I joined Holo, I said in my debut
one of my goals was to make a song for anime.
But really, it's been my lifelong goal to do something like that.
And I've already cried a lot over this, so I'm not going to here,
but I'm very emotional about it. So please look forward to it.
The animation production is by the amazing WIT STUDIO,
so you know it's gonna be a banger. It's incredible.
And I really want everybody to watch it when it comes out.
So please make sure that you stay tuned when it does air.
And there's still something else I'd like to show you.
2024.04.25
NEW SONG RELEASE
WITH ?
COMING SOON
Whoa! What was that? What was that?
New song? But what kind of new song? I don't know.
Is there... are there any guesses in the chat? What could this be?
Well, we don't really have a lot of details about it yet.
But it's a secret for another time. So please
keep your eyes peeled for the big reveal coming sometime soon, I'm sure.
Look forward to it.
Now, that's it for the announcements.
However, there is still one song left.
That's right, because this train doesn't stop moving. No down time, baby.
I'm starting to feel it, but perfect timing.
I'm going to change clothes.
So don't watch me, どダメ！ Look over there!
So don't watch me, absolutely no! Look over there!
Please don't watch a lady change... Whoa! That was fast.
Callie's very fast. Check it.
It's my Wrapper Reaper T-shirts. I have a bunch of different designs.
You can choose your color and stuff like that. They're on the Mori store.
Make sure that you grab yours if you haven't already. It's very neat.
Check it out. I'm very, very proud of this one.
This one in particular I drew myself, so it's very special to me.
Now let's do this last song, you guys.
A song that I've wanted to perform since my early days in HoloEN.
I think you guys will understand why it's so special when you see it.
Everybody, thank you for coming. Let's rock!
This thing on?
ロキ (ROKI) Lyrics/Composition: Mikito-P
ROKI Lyrics/Composition: Mikito-P
Let's go Callie!
Rap and rap and rap and...
Hey!
Rising sun, post-all-nighter at the club,
Gang in sub-box, 6:30, well crank it up.
Second hand Telecaster, pedals in the back
for the boys in the band say "yo!"
Yo!
Spit fire psychics slow down,
ATP's on the bench showdown,
Wanna play like a shylock swing set,
A god can hide forever boy!
Listen well guys and gals, my important talent,
You can't dance around it,
they'll just tie you down.
Boys mayhem!
That's right!
Like a soulman.
Hey you with the bangs and the attitude,
who's the one that's about to go whack-a-bow
Down to!
Don't you get it twisted,
you're the one taking control!
Rocking, rocking out, rapping, rocking roll,
Strumming that guitar to the rhythm
that just won't stop,
Don't stop, let me see you let it out,
rest in peace to any doubt,
You keep rocking, rocking out,
rapping, rocking roll!
Alright so hold up, what's the plan?
Ready first string, banger like "no I can't"!
In the worst case hang around,
sing shit underground, gotta rep not a crown, so what?
Got something to say, you better say it loud,
you got a whack ass sound a little more profound,
As it on and on it goes, on and on and on,
off with the opinions, not by a long shot,
When you're hot gotta take the heat, till then it burn
you both because the street's command,
To stay tough with the make-up, glamour style,
you can fake it for a gangster a little while.
Boys mayhem, like a soul man!
You can't be stopped, seeing break-all-real-fast,
make it last!
Better take a selfie!
Selfie!
You ain't gonna die on me,
we gotta stay alive!
Rocking, rocking out, rapping, rocking roll,
Even songs of love bring emotion
that just won't stop,
Don't stop, she's the flow and my beloved,
she's her world and light it up,
By rocking, rocking out, rapping, rocking roll!
Down!
Give it up for Hololive English Myth Band!
Takanashi Kiara on keyboard!
Ninomae Ina'nis on drums!
Ukulele-go Gura!
Amelia Watson, guitar!
Mori, bass!
So we don't half-ass this, playing to the masses,
marking your ahead is in, now we've passed this,
A-yo, where the pros met us in,
gimme-gimme that compression and apprehension,
Keep stressing the present, leaving 'em guessing,
under the weather, disbelief suspension,
Big sorry guys, if I apologize,
take us to hell, can you tell that my voice is just about to die?
Huh?
I didn't think you could still perform,
but if you guys want to, I don't know...
Better know, get a grip, cut that shit baby!
Baby!
You ain't gonna die on me,
we gotta stay alive!
Rocking, rocking out, rapping, rocking roll,
strumming that guitar to the rhythm that just won't stop,
Don't stop, let me see you let it out,
rest in peace to any doubt,
You keep rocking, rocking out,
rapping, rocking roll!
Rocking, rocking out!
Rapping, rocking roll!
La la la-la-la-la-la...
Proving I won't die!
You ain't dying either!
Music, rap and fire!
It's how we stay alive!
Hell yeah!
Alright!
Thank you everyone!
Myth fucking rocks!
Rap and rap and rock and roll!